[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0401_Watcher_Death",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0401_Watcher_Death_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0401_Watcher_Death_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0401_Watcher_Corruption",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0401_Watcher_Corruption_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0401_Watcher_Corruption_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0402_Magistrate_Everfall",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0402_Magistrate_Everfall_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0402_Magistrate_Everfall_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0402_Magistrate_FactionsReady",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0402_Magistrate_FactionsReady_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0402_Magistrate_Factions_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_factionchoiceready",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_factiontalkedto",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0422_Innkeep_WhereNow",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0422_Innkeep_WhereNow_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0422_Innkeep_WhereNow_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0422_Innkeep_WhyHouse",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0422_Innkeep_WhyHouse_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0422_Innkeep_WhyHouse_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Survivalist0403_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@Survivalist0403_01_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@Survivalist0403_01_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0402_Marauder_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0402_Marauder_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0402_Marauder_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_introtomarauders",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_introtoallfactions_accepted",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0402_Syndicate_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0402_Syndicate_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0402_Syndicate_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_introtosyndicate",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_introtoallfactions_accepted",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0402_Covenant_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0402_Covenant_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0402_Covenant_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_introtocovenant",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_introtoallfactions_accepted",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0402_Marauder_dye_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0402_Marauder_dye_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0402_Marauder_dye_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_marauderquest1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0402_Syndicate_dye_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0402_Syndicate_dye_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0402_Syndicate_dye_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_syndicatequest1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0402_Covenant_dye_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0402_Covenant_dye_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0402_Covenant_dye_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_covenantquest1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0404_Constable_EncroachingCorruption",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0404_Constable_EncroachingCorruption_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0404_Constable_EncroachingCorruption",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_encroachingconstable",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0423_Fisher_ExplainHotspots",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0428_Jones_Market",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0428_Jones_Market_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0428_Jones_Market_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0428_Jones_Tips",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0428_Jones_Tips_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0428_Jones_Tips_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0428_Jones_House",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0428_Jones_House_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0428_Jones_House_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 20
    }
]
